Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XIII. CITY CENTRAL BODIES
  - Sub-Series 213-98. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. District 50, United Mine Workers of America-Railroad Workers Industrial Union Division, 1944-1945 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      1944-July 1945.
    - Jurisdiction. District 50, United Mine Workers of America-Railroad Workers Industrial Union Division, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      July 1, 1943-Dec. 9, 1943.
    - Jurisdiction. District 50, United Mine Workers of America-Railroad Workers Industrial Union Division, 1942-1943 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      1942-June 22, 1943.
  - Sub-Series 213-99. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Federation of Labor (A. F. of L.) and Congress of Industrial Organizations (C. I. O.), 1942-1954 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 213-100. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. U. R. E. U. (?), 1943-1950 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 213-101. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Transport Workers Union of America, CIO, 1948-1959 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Jurisdiction. Transport Workers Union of America, CIO, 1945-1947 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-102. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1945-1954 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-103. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. National Organization of Masters, Mates & Pilots of America, 1945-1950 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 213-104. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Association of Railroad Employees, 1945-1954 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 213-105. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Operating Railroad Employees of the United States of America, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 213-106. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1946-1956 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 213-108. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen of America, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 213-109. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Air Line Communication Employees Association-Airline Department, American Communications Association, CIO, 1946-1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 213-110. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Air Line Pilots Association, 1946-1957 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 213-111. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Air Line Mechanics Department, United Automobile Workers (UAW), CIO, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 213-112. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Federation of Technical Engineers, Architects and Draftmen's Union, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 213-113. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Railroad Employees' Organization, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 213-114. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Big Six Brotherhood, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 213-115. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railway Conductors, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 213-116. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Alliance Bill Posters, Billers and Distributors of U. S. and Canada, 1947-1953 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 213-117. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Railroad Industrial Union, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 213-118. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Radio Officers' Union-Pan American Airways, Inc., 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 213-119. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Federation of Grain Millers, 1948-1951 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 213-120. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Shop Crafts-Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 213-121. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Yardmasters & Stationmasters Association, Inc., 1949 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 213-122. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Foremen's Association of America, Great Lakes Licensed Officers' Amalgamated Marine Chapter No. 159, 1949-1951 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 213-123. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1949-1951 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 213-124. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Office Employees International Union, AFL, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 213-125. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Communications Association, 1949-1951 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 213-126. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Radio Association, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 213-128. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Maintenance of Way-Central of Georgia, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 213-129. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Pullman Clerks' Association, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 213-130. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Radio Operators-Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 213-131. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. The Federated Airlines Workers of America, Unaffiliated, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 213-132. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Express Workers Union, 1950-1955 (Box 61, Folder 36)
      Dec. 1950-55.
    - Jurisdiction. Express Workers Union, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 37)
      Jan. 1950-Nov. 1950.
    - Jurisdiction? Record of Proceedings-International Labour Conference, Forty-Sixth Session, Geneva (bound volume), 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction. Express Workers Union, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 213-133. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1949-1953 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 213-134. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Joint Council Dining Car Employees, AFL, 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 213-135. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Air Line & Stewardesses Association, International, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 213-137. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. United Railroad Workers of America, 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 213-138. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 213-139. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Utility Service & Maintenance Workers, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 213-140. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Printing Pressmen's and Assistants Union of North America, 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 213-141. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Great Lakes Licensed Officers Organization, 1950-1951 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 213-142. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Air Line Agents Association, 1950-1957 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 213-143. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Railroad Yardmasters of North America, 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 213-144. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. American Federation of Grain Millers, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 213-145. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Railway Passenger Service Employees Union, CIO, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 213-146. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Terminal Employees Association-Kansas City, Missouri, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 213-147. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. National Maritime Union, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 213-148. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. California State Building and Construction Trades Council, 1951-1954 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 213-149. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Dietitians-Southern Pacific Hospital Department, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 213-150. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Sky Caps-Capital Airlines, Inc., 1952-1956 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 213-151. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. United Packinghouse Workers, CIO, 1953-1957 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 213-152. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. The Union National of Workers of Quebec Harbors, Inc., 1953 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 213-153. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers of America, AFL, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 213-154. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Independent Railroad Workers of America, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 213-156. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, AFL, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Jurisdiction. International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, AFL, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 213-204-57. City Central Bodies
    - Jurisdiction. Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1959-1962 (Box 62, Folder 26)
      Sept. 9, 1959-62.